Guide to the Leah Fritz Papers, 1940-2009 and undated RL.10134
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Leah Fritz papers
circa 1950-2009 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture
Fritz, Leah
RL.10134
17 Linear Feet
Leah Fritz is an American feminist poet and author. Although she was born in the United States, Fritz has been active in England since she moved there in 1985. The Leah Fritz papers contain correspondence and subject files; writings, including notebooks and diaries, drafts, published articles, and papers related to the publication of Fritz's prose writings, poetry, and book and article reviews; and audiocassettes of presentations and poetry readings by Fritz and other recordings. Materials range in date from circa 1950 to 2009.
Provenance
The Leah Fritz papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a purchase in February 2010 and as a gift in April 2010.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Arrangement
The Correspondence subseries is arranged chronologically. The Subject Files subseries and the Writings and Audiotapes series are arranged alphabetically by title.
Related Materials
Phyllis Chesler Papers, 1968-1990 (Duke University. David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library) Robin Morgan Papers, 1940s-2010 and undated, bulk 1970-2000 (Duke University. David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library)
Collection Overview
The Leah Fritz papers are organized into three series. The Personal Papers series contains Leah Fritz's correspondence and subject files. The Writings Series contains Fritz's notebooks and diaries as well as drafts, published articles, and papers related to the publication of Fritz's prose writings, poetry, and book and article reviews. The Audiotapes series contains audiocassettes of presentations and poetry readings by Fritz and other recordings.
Historical note
Leah Fritz is an American feminist poet and author. Although she was born in the United States, Fritz has been active in England since she moved there in 1985. Prior to immigrating to England, Fritz primarily wrote essays, articles, and other prose pieces. She published two books in the United States: Thinking Like a Woman and Dreamers and Dealers: An Intimate Appraisal of the Women's Movement. Although she had written poetry since her childhood, Fritz did not focus her career on poetry until she moved to England. She has published several poetry collections, including From Cookie to Witch is an Old Story, Somewhere En Route - Poems, 1987-1992, The Way to Go, Going, Going..., and Whatever Sends the Music into Time: New and Selected Poems. Fritz currently lives in London.
Feminist poetry, English.; Sex -- Psychological aspects.; Pornography -- Social aspects -- United States.; Feminism and literature -- Great Britain -- History -- 20th century.; Women poets, English.; International Women's Day.; Educational change -- United States.; Feminism -- Poetry.; Feminism -- Religious aspects.; Morgan, Robin, 1941-; Dworkin, Andrea; Chesler, Phyllis; Brownmiller, Susan.; Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture; PEN (Organization); Writer's Guild of Great Britain; Deming, Barbara; Johnson, Adam; Dorcey, Mary; Rumens, Carol.
- Personal Papers series, 1962-2009 and undated; 14 boxes
  Scope and Contents
  The Personal Papers series contains Leah Fritz's correspondence and subject files. The Correspondence subseries contains letters to and from Leah Fritz, primarily related to her writings. Family correspondence and post cards appear throughout the subseries. A folder labeled "Unmailable Letters" apparently contains drafts of critical, controversial, or otherwise personal letters that Fritz never sent. There are also several folders of greeting cards, almost all of which include letters or substantial notes from correspondents. The Subject Files series contains research materials and subject files on various individuals, organizations, publications and events. Folders identified with the names of authors, poets, activists and other individuals contain correspondence and other papers related to their works.
  - Correspondence subseries, 1962-2009 and undated; 5 boxes
    The Correspondence subseries contains letters to and from Leah Fritz, primarily related to her writings. Family correspondence and post cards appear throughout the subseries. A folder labeled "Unmailable Letters" apparently contains drafts of critical, controversial, or otherwise personal letters that Fritz never sent. There are also several folders of greeting cards, almost all of which include letters or substantial notes from correspondents.
    Arrangement
    Chronological.
    - 1962-1987, 8 folders (Box 1)
    - 1988-1990, 7 folders (Box 2)
    - 1991-1996, 8 folders (Box 3)
    - 1997-2009, 3 folders (Box 4)
    - Undated, 3 folders (Box 4)
    - Unmailable Letters, 1977-1982; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Greeting cards, 1986-2009 and undated; 6 folders (Box 5)
  - Subject Files subseries, 1966-2009 and undated; 8 boxes
    Alphabetical by folder title.
    The Subject Files series contains research materials and subject files on various individuals, organizations, publications and events. Folders identified with the names of authors, poets, activists and other individuals contain correspondence and other papers related to their works.
    - Acumen, undated (Box 6)
    - Adam Johnson and Joyce Johnson, undated (Box 6)
    - Amy Fritz- Journeys of the Imagination: Metaphor and Meaning, 1984 (Box 6)
    - Articles by Andie Hawthorn, undated (Box 6)
    - Alan Brown John, undated (Box 6)
    - Alix K. Shulman, Sojourner, Thinking Like a Woman, undated (Box 6)
    - Andrea Dworkin, undated (Box 6)
    - Anita Hoffman, undated (Box 6)
    - Article by Anita Hoffman, undated (Box 6)
    - Anna Adams, undated (Box 6)
    - Auberon Waugh, Denise Lavendar, John Heath-Stubbs, Antonia Fraser, Aeron Thomas, undated (Box 6)
    - Author's Licensing and Collecting Society Limited, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Autobiography of Marge Piercy, undated (Box 6)
    - Barbara Deming and Jane Verlaine, undated; 2 folders (Box 6-7)
    - Barbican, undated (Box 7)
    - Beacon Press, undated (Box 7)
    - China Information, Patricia Goldstone, Patricia Hearst, undated (Box 7)
    - Chrysalis, undated (Box 7)
    - Deepening the Mystery, Cristiana Maria Purdescu, Translated by Leah Fritz, 2009 (Box 7)
    - Dorothy Caune, "Say It Isn't So: A Partial Examination of Feminist Anthropologists' Theory and Application", 1978 (Box 7)
    - Edward D. Jeffries, Inside Our Black Schools, undated (Box 7)
    - Ellen Frankfurt, Phyllis Chesler, Elizabeth Fisher, undated (Box 7)
    - English Centre of International P.E.N., 1985-1996 (Box 7)
    - Feminist Review, Women's Revew of Books, undated (Box 7)
    - Feminist Publications, undated (Box 7)
    - Feminist Writer's Guild, undated (Box 8)
    - Flo Kennedy, undated (Box 8)
    - Greta Rana, undated (Box 8)
    - Draft of Intercourse by Andrea Dworkin, undated; 3 folders (Box 8)
    - International Network of Women Writers, 1991 (Box 8)
    - International P.E.N. 56th World Congress, Vienna, 1991 (Box 8)
    - Internationale Vrouwendag [International Women's Day] memorabilia, circa 1980 (Box 8)
    - Internationale Vrouwendag [International Women's Day] tote bag, circa 1980 (Box 31)
    - Jeremy Mulferd, undated (Box 8)
    - Joanna Briscoe, Mothers and Lovers, 1994 (Box 9)
    - Judi Benson, Sebastian Barker, undated (Box 9)
    - Karen Lindsey, Marcie Piercy, undated (Box 9)
    - Karen Malpede, Emily Jane Goodman, Yvonne Klein, Sandra Elkin, Gloria Orenstein, undated (Box 9)
    - Karla Jay, Elaine Workson, Erica Jong, undated (Box 9)
    - Kathy Kample, E.M. Broner, undated (Box 9)
    - A Langston Hughes Memorial Evening, 1967 (Box 9)
    - Last Will and Testament of Esther Hurwit, 1978 (Box 9)
    - L.A. Times: Art Seldenbaum, Book Reviews, etc., undated (Box 9)
    - Louise Armstrong, undated (Box 9)
    - Louise Bernikow, Susan Brownmiller, Erika Duncan, undated (Box 9)
    - Memberships, undated (Box 9)
    - Michael Schmidt, undated (Box 9)
    - Michelle Wallace, Pam Wyles, undated (Box 9)
    - Miscellaneous financial, undated (Box 9)
    - Miscellaneous political info, undated (Box 9)
    - Money for Women, undated (Box 10)
    - Ms. Magazine, undated (Box 10)
    - Ms. Magazine violence survey, 1991 (Box 10)
    - Nancy Mattson, Mike Bartholomew-Biggs, undated (Box 10)
    - NARAL, Corrine Oudyk, undated (Box 10)
    - National Women's Conference, Houston, 1977 (Box 10)
    - Newsletters, undated; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Painting by an unknown artist, "Having Fun with Poster Paint", circa 1995 (Box 10)
    - Pamphlets and Flyers, 2 folders (Box 10-11)
    - P.E.N. International Congress Tokyo, 1984 (Box 11)
    - P.E.N. and Writer's Guild, undated (Box 11)
    - Periodicals, 1966-1976 (Box 11)
    - Petra Kenney Poetry Competition, undated (Box 11)
    - Photographs, circa 1970-1995 and undated (Box 11)
      Contains photographs of Leah Fritz, circa 1980; a performance of an unknown play by the Women and Theatre Friends Institute; Cildo Meireles's Olvido (Oblivion) at the Museum of Modern art, 1989; a man on horse labeled "Dick on Georgia's horse - before I framed it;" clouds over a set of chimneys in England; framed photographs hanging on a wall; unidentified family (labeled with the names Harry, Silas, and Kristen), 1995; and an unknown man labeled "A talented young poet," circa 1970. Also includes a photocopy of a photograph labeled "Howard and Leah Fritz and Shere Hite's aunt at her birthday party hosted by Shere Hite at a Paris Restaurant."
    - Poetry readings, 1997-2009 (Box 11)
    - The Poetry Society, 1991-1993 (Box 12)
    - Poetry Society Extraordinary general meeting, 1991 (Box 12)
    - Rhona McAdam, undated (Box 12)
    - Robin Morgan, Grace Paley, Adrienne Rich, Gloria Steinem, Jane Alpert, undated (Box 12)
    - Russell Baker and Thomas Szasz, undated (Box 12)
    - Sarah Lawson, undated (Box 12)
    - Seneca Falls, Janet Steinberg, Honor Moore, undated (Box 12)
    - Shere Hite, undated (Box 12)
    - Sonia Johnson, undated (Box 12)
    - Speaking engagements before 1985, undated (Box 12)
    - Torriano Meeting House, undated (Box 12)
    - War Resister's League, undated (Box 12)
    - Watershed, June 1987 (Box 13)
    - Wendy Mulford, Late Spring Next Year, 1987 (Box 13)
    - Women Against Pornography, Dorchen Leidholt, 1987 (Box 13)
    - Writer's Guild of Great Britain, 1989-1991; 3 folders (Box 13)
    - Writer's Guild of Great Britain Women's Committee meetings, 1989-1992 (Box 13)
    - Loose papers, undated (Box 13)
- Writings series, undated; 17 boxes
  The Writings Series contains Fritz's notebooks and diaries as well as drafts, published articles, and papers related to the publication of Fritz's prose writings, poetry, and book and article reviews. The Notebooks and Diaries subseries contains Fritz's diaries, notebooks, address books, and other volumes. Most of the volumes contain irregular diary entries, reflections, poetry drafts, and drawings. The Prose Subseries contains drafts and published versions of Fritz's essays, articles, letters to the editor, and other prose pieces. The bulk of these materials predate Fritz's emigration to England. Included in this series are drafts of Fritz's book, Dreamers and Dealers: An Intimate Appraisal of the Women's Movement. Also included are clippings, notes, and editorial comments on Fritz's work and an article submission index tracking the publications and journals to which Fritz submitted her writings. The Poetry subseries includes poetry manuscripts; drafts and proofs of Fritz's published poetry anthologies, including From Cookie to Witch is an Old Story, Going, Going..., Somewhere En Route - Poems, 1987-1992, The Way to Go, and an apparently unpublished collection of poems, Bureau de Change; materials related to the publication of Touching the Sun, an anthology dedicated to the memory of poet Adam Johnson, edited by Fritz; and other papers. The Book Reviews subseries contains drafts and published versions of Fritz's reviews of books, articles, and poetry.
  - Notebooks and Diaries subseries, 1960-1987 and undated; 3 boxes
    Alphabetical by format; chronological within formats.
    The Notebooks and Diaries subseries contains Fritz's diaries, notebooks, address books, and other volumes. Most of the volumes contain irregular diary entries, reflections, poetry drafts, and drawings.
    - Address books, undated; 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Desk diary, 1987 (Box 14)
    - Diary, 1960-1961 (Box 14)
    - Diary, 1969 (Box 14)
    - Diary, 1979-1981 (Box 14)
    - Notebook, 1976-1977 (Box 15)
    - Notebook, 1985 (Box 15)
    - Notebooks, undated; 10 folders (Box 15-16)
    - Scrapbook, 1965-1967; 1 folders (Box 16)
  - Prose subseries, circa 1950-1993 and undated; 9 boxes
    Alphabetical by title or subject.
    The Prose Subseries contains drafts and published versions of Fritz's essays, articles, letters to the editor, and other prose pieces. The bulk of these materials predate Fritz's emigration to England. Included in this series are drafts of Fritz's book, Dreamers and Dealers: An Intimate Appraisal of the Women's Movement. Also included are clippings, notes, and editorial comments on Fritz's work and an article submission index tracking the publications and journals to which Fritz submitted her writings.
    - Abortion as Sacrament, 1981 (Box 17)
    - Accident of Birth, undated; 5 folders (Box 17)
    - Address at Earl Hall, Columbia University, 6 March 1979 (Box 17)
    - Untitled address, undated (Box 17)
    - An Apology for My Life, 1968-1969 (Box 18)
    - ...And the Victory "Over Ourselves", 1977 (Box 18)
    - Are Public School Children Guinea Pigs/The Mt. Sinai School Project, undated (Box 18)
    - Art and the Hierarchy, undated (Box 18)
    - Back to Basics: Consciousness Raising Around Sexual Fantasies, undated (Box 18)
    - Eulogy for Barbara Deming, undated (Box 18)
    - Barbara Deming: The Rage of a Pacifist, 1978 (Box 18)
    - Becoming a Real Woman of the World, 1980 (Box 18)
    - Between Friends: Shere Hite and Leah Fritz, undated (Box 18)
    - The Bold Invader, undated (Box 18)
    - Brother to Thoreau, 1965 (Box 18)
    - Camping Out in Romulus: The Women's Encampment for a Future of Peace and Justice, undated (Box 18)
    - Untitled manuscript on childhood memories, undated (Box 18)
    - Prospectus: The City, a Magazine of Integrated City Living, undated (Box 18)
    - Clearwater Reflections, undated (Box 18)
    - Clit-Chat, undated (Box 18)
    - Community Control of Our Schools, 1968 (Box 18)
    - The Composer and the Accountant, undated (Box 18)
    - Courtney, undated (Box 18)
    - A Current Report on Communal Bliss, undated (Box 18)
    - The Day MOMA Lost Her Cherry, undated (Box 18)
    - Devotions of a Feminist Atheist, 1990 (Box 19)
    - Does the Women's Movement Scare Women?, 1980 (Box 19)
    - Dr. B's Office, undated (Box 19)
    - Dreamers and Dealers: An Intimate Appraisal of the Women's Movement, 1979 and undated; 4 folders (Box 19)
    - Dreamers and Dealers correspondence, 1978-1982 (Box 19)
    - Reviews of Dreamers and Dealers: An Intimate Appraisal of the Women's Movement, undated (Box 19)
    - Esthetics in Education, undated (Box 20)
    - Eulogy, undated (Box 20)
    - The Expensive Spirit, undated (Box 20)
    - Feminism and Individualism: Who Pays the Piper?, undated (Box 20)
    - Feminism, Pacifism, and Self-Defense, 1983 (Box 20)
    - Feminist Psychotherapy, undated (Box 20)
    - Feminist Publishing in the United Kingdom, undated (Box 20)
    - A Few Words with a Madame of Literature Who Asked Me to Write a Six-Page Confidential Autobiography, undated (Box 20)
    - Finding Truth, Facing Consequences, 1980 (Box 20)
    - Friends, undated (Box 20)
    - The Frustration of a Day in Washington, 1967 (Box 20)
    - A Gathering of Writers, 1988 (Box 20)
    - Ghetto Fears, undated (Box 20)
    - Goldilocks, undated (Box 20)
    - The Highwayman, undated (Box 20)
    - Hiroshima mon amour, 1966 (Box 20)
    - Homage Toward..., undated (Box 20)
    - The Horn of Plenty, undated (Box 20)
    - Houston Journal: A Personal Memoir of the National Women's Conference, 1977 (Box 20)
    - How to Be a Bitch, undated (Box 20)
    - How to Make Love to the New Woman (A Guide for the New Man), undated (Box 20)
    - How to Make a Million (Through Female), undated (Box 20)
    - Images of Women: Robin Morgan and Adrienne Rich, undated (Box 20)
    - In Defense of Non-Lesbian Women, undated (Box 20)
    - In the Eighties- "You Can't Scare Me, I'm Sticking to the Movement", 1979 (Box 20)
    - The Intelligent Man's Guide to Sexism, undated (Box 20)
    - International P.E.N. Conference, 1988 (Box 20)
    - International Women's Day, undated (Box 20)
    - Interview with Andrea Dworkin, undated (Box 20)
    - Interview with Mary Dorcey, undated (Box 20)
    - Interview with Susan Brownmiller, undated (Box 20)
    - Introduction to a Guidebook on New York, undated (Box 21)
    - Introduction: In Which My Fingers Do the Talking, undated (Box 21)
    - Is the East Side Culturally Hip?, 1966 (Box 21)
    - Is there Sex After Sadomasochism?, 1983 (Box 21)
    - J'Acuse Alfred Hitchcock and groucho marks, undated (Box 21)
    - The Jewish Mother and the Prodigal Son, undated (Box 21)
    - Key West: The Week of the Refugees, 1980 (Box 21)
    - The Lamp, undated (Box 21)
    - The Last Full Measure, undated (Box 21)
    - The Last Minute is Now chapter outline, undated (Box 21)
    - Letter to the editor on the Women's Liberation Movement, 1982 (Box 21)
    - A Letter to My Mother, Laying it on the Line, undated (Box 21)
    - Proposal for Living with Children, undated (Box 21)
    - The Loneliness of the Long-Distance Smoker, undated (Box 21)
    - The Long View: Perspectives on Modern Feminism, undated; 6 folders (Box 21-22)
    - Love, Sweet Love, You're Turning Me Off, undated (Box 22)
    - Mary Lou, undated (Box 22)
    - Mirror, Mirror, undated (Box 22)
    - A Mirrored Room, undated (Box 22)
    - Money: A Declaration of Independence, 1975 (Box 22)
    - The More Things Change, undated (Box 22)
    - The Name of the Game- "Doing it for Free", 1967 (Box 22)
    - A Night Story, undated (Box 22)
    - New York City School Decentralization, undated (Box 22)
    - Nobody Stands on the Sun, undated (Box 22)
    - Not Immediately, undated (Box 22)
    - Notes on a Quandary, undated (Box 23)
    - Nothing to Confess (A Confession), undated (Box 23)
    - Ocean Hill- Brownsville, undated (Box 23)
    - On Atheism and Spirituality, undated (Box 23)
    - On the Barnard Conference, "The Scholar and the Feminist IX...", 1982 (Box 23)
    - On Criticism and Survival, undated (Box 23)
    - On E. Babette Edwards, undated (Box 23)
    - On Ellen Willis, 1981 (Box 23)
    - On Mary Dorcey, undated (Box 23)
    - On the New Feminist Criticism, undated (Box 23)
    - Or What's a Heaven For?, undated (Box 23)
    - P.E.N. in Tokyo, 1984 (Box 23)
    - Pilgrims and Indians, undated (Box 23)
    - Playboy Protest, undated (Box 23)
    - Pornography, Domestic Violence, and Criminal Justice, 1984 (Box 23)
    - Pornography as Genocidal Propaganda, 1978-1979 (Box 23)
    - Untitled article on pornography, 1979 (Box 23)
    - The Press of Freedom: Article on SNCC, 1967 (Box 23)
    - P.S. 6-P.S. 198, undated (Box 23)
    - P.S. 198 Hangup- "Psyched" Kids, 1967 (Box 23)
    - Untitled article on public education, undated (Box 23)
    - Publishing and flourishing, 1986 (Box 23)
    - Query for a Profile on Sonia Johnson, undated (Box 23)
    - Radical Feminism: The Greatest Hope, 1984 (Box 23)
    - Report on Liberation, undated (Box 23)
    - Rock and Rule, undated (Box 23)
    - Romeo and Juliet, undated (Box 23)
    - Lecture on sadomasochism and pornography, 1983 (Box 23)
    - Schools/The School Front, 1966-1968 (Box 23)
    - Sex and Revolution, undated (Box 23)
    - Sex in Transition, undated (Box 23)
    - The Sexual Autobiography of a Middle-Aged Straight Radical Feminist, undated (Box 24)
    - Sigmund Freud Meets the Women's Movement, undated (Box 24)
    - The Sign on the Door, undated (Box 24)
    - Snuff Obscenity Trial in Monticello, undated (Box 24)
    - So Long at the Fart, undated (Box 24)
    - Socialism vs. Feminism: What Are Our Priorities?, undated (Box 24)
    - Sometimes I Feel like a Motherless Child, undated (Box 24)
    - The Space to Succeed, the Space to Fail, 1989 (Box 24)
    - Subverting Sexual Stereotypes, undated (Box 24)
    - The Squirrel Story, undated (Box 24)
    - The Swindle I: The New Buildings, 1963 (Box 24)
    - Tangled Vines and Ordinary Women, undated (Box 24)
    - Team Teaching a Loser, 1967 (Box 24)
    - Thinking Like a Woman, undated (Box 24)
    - Title I, undated (Box 24)
    - Toward a Definition of Feminism, undated (Box 24)
    - Two Stories for the Teacher, undated (Box 24)
    - An Unmanifesto, 1973 (Box 24)
    - Up in the Gymnasium, 1993 (Box 24)
    - Vacation, circa 1950 (Box 24)
    - Vigil for Margaretta D'Arcy, 1979 (Box 24)
    - WAP Speakout on Pornography, 1982 (Box 24)
    - What a Piece She Was!, undated (Box 24)
    - What Women Writers Want for the World, undated (Box 24)
    - What's Going On Here? Art and the Movement, 1968 (Box 24)
    - Why Old Habit Diehards Never Take the Cure, 1988 (Box 24)
    - Why We Had to Picket "Snuff", 1976 (Box 24)
    - WLWC-WAP Panel on "Radical Feminist Perspectives: Disarming the patriarchy"- Introductory remarks, 1982 (Box 24)
    - Proposal for Women Who Defy the Gods, 1991 (Box 24)
    - Women's Liberation Atlantic City: The Personal View of a Married Woman, undated (Box 24)
    - The Writer and Women's Rights, 1984 (Box 24)
    - Anthologies, undated (Box 24)
    - Article submission index, undated (Box 24)
    - Clippings, undated (Box 24)
    - Editor's comments, undated (Box 25)
    - Notes, undated (Box 25)
    - Unidentified book draft, undated (Box 25)
    - Untitled drafts, undated (Box 25)
    - Unidentified manuscript fragments, undated; 3 folders (Box 25)
  - Poetry subseries, 1980-2009 and undated; 4 boxes
    Alphabetical by title
    The Poetry subseries includes poetry manuscripts; drafts and proofs of Fritz's published poetry anthologies, including From Cookie to Witch is an Old Story, Going, Going..., Somewhere En Route - Poems, 1987-1992, The Way to Go, and an apparently unpublished collection of poems, Bureau de Change; materials related to the publication of Touching the Sun, an anthology dedicated to the memory of poet Adam Johnson, edited by Fritz; and other papers.
    - Britain Readings, 1992-2009 (Box 26)
    - Bureau de Change drafts, 1980; 3 folders (Box 26)
    - A Celebration of the Life of Adam Johnson, 1993 (Box 26)
    - Exeter Poetry Prize Anthology, 1997 (Box 26)
    - From Cookie to Witch is an Old Story, 1987-2004 (Box 26)
    - From Cookie to Witch is an Old Story- book release, undated (Box 26)
    - Going, Going..., 2007 (Box 26)
    - Going, Going... proofs, undated (Box 27)
    - Poems submitted to Ambit magazine, undated (Box 27)
    - A Poet's ABC: An Encyclopedia in Verse for Children 8 to 14, undated (Box 27)
    - Somewhere En Route, 1987-1992 (Box 27)
    - Touching the Sun: Poems in Memory of Adam Johnson, 1993-1995 (Box 27)
    - Touching the Sun launch, undated (Box 27)
    - The Way to Go, 1999 (Box 27)
    - Poetry manuscripts, undated; 15 folders (Box 27-29)
  - Book Reviews subseries, 1966-2001 and undated; 1 boxes
    Alphabetical by title.
    The Book Reviews subseries contains drafts and published versions of Fritz's reviews of books, articles, and poetry.
    - Alone: Yearning for Companionship in America- Louise Berkinow, 1982 (Box 30)